- It's been a while.
- 久しぶりだね
- 久しぶりです
- How have you been?
- 元気だった?
- Yes, I was fine.
- はい、元気でした
- copper?
- どう?
Previous shoot.
前の撮影
- It was embarrassing.
- 恥ずかしかったです
- We're getting along much better than before.
- 前よりかは、めっちゃ仲良くなってきてるんだけどね
- yes.
- はい
- By the way, Minami-chan is quite dressed up, isn't she?
- そりゃ、美奈美ちゃんって、結構ドレになってんの?
- yes.
- はい
- What about before?
- 前からどう?
Did you do any other filming?
他の撮影をやったりした?
Or?
したり?
- You didn't.
- お前、してないです
- Oh, haven't you?
- あ、してない?
- yes.
- はい
- The previous shoot was pretty golden, wasn't it?
- 前の撮影は結構、黄金した?
- yes.
- はい
- Well then, that's good.
- じゃ、よかった
- Yeah.
- うん
- I haven't heard anything about it today.
- 今日なんて、内容とか聞いてないよね
- yes.
- はい
- Hey, it goes well with the back side, when you're wearing a costume.
- ちょっと、裏面に合う、コスチュームの時に
- Yeah.
- うん
- I want you to change your clothes and have sex with me.
- それ着替えて、エッチしてほしい
- Heh heh heh.
- えっへっへっへ
- good?
- いい?
- yes.
- はい
- Well, for now, can I have you change your clothes?
- じゃ、とりあえず、着替えてもらっていい?
- yes.
- はい
-
You guessed right?
当 てるよね?
- yes.
- はい
- Do you understand?
- わかる?
- Is it a sailor uniform?
- セーラー服ですか?
- Are you wearing something?
- なんか、ちょっと着けてる?
- No, no.
- いない、違う
- Sailor suit, blazer suit.
- セーラー服、ブレザー服
- It was a blazer.
- ブレザーでした
- Well, it's fresh.
- じゃ、新鮮でいいね
- yes.
- はい
- Can I have you change your clothes?
- 着替えてもらっていい?
- yes.
- はい
- It suits you really well.
- め っちゃ似合うね
- Heh heh heh.
- えっへっへっ
- I see, there was also a young child.
- な んか、幼な子もしたね
- Huh, that's embarrassing.
- えっへっ、恥ずかしい
- It suits you really well.
- めちゃくちゃ似合ってる
- Yeah.
- うん
- Rock, paper, scissors before club activities.
- 部活の前じゃんけん
- Heh heh heh.
- えっへっへっ
- Your legs are long.
- 足長いね
- Yes, thank you.
- うん、ありがとうございます
- Oh, that's not true.
- あ、そりゃそうじゃない
- Eh heh heh, it's embarrassing.
- えっへっへっへ、恥ずかしい
- Hey, what's going on behind you?
- ちょっと、後ろどうなってんの?
- Huh?
- えっ?
- My waist is round.
- 腰、丸になっちゃってる
- Heh heh heh.
- えっへっへっ
-
In that case, try your hand at it.
そ の場合、手ついてみて
- yes.
- はい
- It's embarrassing.
- 恥ずかしい
-
I have to align this with the center line properly.
ち ゃんと、これ、センターラインに合わせないとさ
- yes.
- はい
- Can you put it here?
- ここにつける?
- Yeah.
- うん
- Legs.
- 足のね
- I like the style.
- スタイルいいね
- Ah.
- あっ
- Her legs are amazing too.
- ここ足もすごい
- Yeah.
- うん
- Try opening your legs.
- 足開いてみて
- yes.
- はい
- I'm wearing it.
- 付けちゃってるよ
- Heh heh heh.
- えっへっへっ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
- Don't you usually wear something like this?
- 普段、こういうの着ないの?
- Hmm, I won't wear it.
- うーん、着ないです
- Do you have any work at Spresh?
- スプレッシュとか、仕事ない?
- yes.
- はい
-
This is how it looks.
こ うやって見えちゃうって
- Huh?
- えっへっ
- It happened when you turned the corner, right?
- コーナーした時起きたんでしょ?
- yes.
- はい
- Corner?
- コーナーする?
- yes.
- はい
- Did you feel that way?
- って感じたの?
- Heh heh heh.
- えっへっへっ
- this is?
- これは?
- Corner and open.
- コーナーし開いて
- yes.
- はい
- Will it get hard?
- 固くなっちゃう?
- no.
- いや
- It's embarrassing.
- 恥ずかしいです
- 恥ずかしい
- Look, I got it.
- ほら、取れちゃった
- Yeah.
- うん
I like it.
好きです
- Do you really want it?
- 本当にしてほしい?
- Yes, please.
- うん、してください
I want you to touch it a lot.
いっぱい触ってほしいです
- Really?
- 本当に?
- Huh?
- えっへっ
Please make yourself comfortable.
気持ちよくしてください
- where?
- どこ?
- Heh heh heh.
- えっへっへっ
- Really?
- 本当に?
- Yeah.
- うん
I want you to touch lots of chestnuts.
栗とか、いっぱい触ってほしいです
I love chestnuts so much.
栗とかって、そんなに栗が好きなのに
- Eh heh heh.
- え っへっへっ
- Yeah.
- うん
- Where do you want me to place this?
- これどこに当てほしいの?
- Heh heh heh heh.
- えっへっへっへっ
Please put it on the chestnut.
栗に当ててください
- Yeah?
- うん?
- Huh?
- えっへっ
Please put it on the chestnut.
栗に当ててください
- Don't do anything.
- 何かしないでください
- yes.
- はい
- Is it interesting?
- 面白いですか?
- Yeah.
- うん
- Stroke while doing this.
- これしながら撫でてください
- yes.
- はい
- cormorant
- う
yeah.
ん
- Yeah.
- うん
- う ん
- Yeah.
- うん
- う ん
- Do you want me to sleep?
- 寝てほしい?
- Yeah.
- うん
- boring.
- つまらない
- It was shown to my face for the first time.
- 初めて顔に出されました
It felt good.
気持ちよかったです